A Finding Aid to the Francis V. O'Connor Papers, 1920-2009, in the Archives of American Art AAA.oconfran
Archives of American Art
- NCFA Library, 1920-1973; Series 1; 6.7 Linear feet Boxes 1-7, OV 28
  - GSA Artists' Employment History Records, 1936-1973; 1.3
    - M-Mc, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 138)
      Forms for the following artists: Mac Baisey, Lionel; Mack, Harry; Macraleigh, Conrad; Mahl, Clare; Malkin, May; Mandelman, Beatrice; Manfredi, Joseph; Mangor, Elizabeth; Maniaci, Nino; Manning, Virginia; Mantell, Ann; Maralian, Arsen; Marder, Ida; Margoles, Isidor; Margolies, Samuel; Markham, Kyra; Markow, Jack; Markowska, Jennie; Marsh, Gregory; Marsh, Reginald; Marshack, Daniel; Marshall, Frederick; Martin, Fletcher; Marvel, Josiah P.; Maslow, Bess; Mastrangelo, Charles E.; Matthews, Arthur; Mattox, Charles; Mattson, Charles A.; Mattson, Henry; Maxey, Stevens; May, Ada W.; Mayer, Bena Frank; Mayer, Herbert; Mayer, Julius; Mayer, Ralph; Mayne, Nicholas; Mazel, Fanny; Mazo, Dorothy; McAusland, Helen; McBride, Hubbell; McCausland, Elizabeth; McCliment, Susan; McCown (McGown), Eugene; McKearin, Helen A.; McMahon, Audrey; McManus, Mildred; McNulty, William J.
    - Md-Mz, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 139)
      Forms for the following artists: Means, Elliott; Meloy, Henry J.; Meltzer, Doris; Melvy, Henry; Merkley, Arthur G.; Merritt, Daniel Chase; Meyer, Herman; Meyerowitz, William; Meyers, Joseph; Meyerson, Sylvia; Middleton, Owen; Mierisch, Dorothea; Milavsky, Bertha; Miller, Ben; Miller, Frances T.; Miller, Hugh; Miller, Natalie V.; Mims, Thomas; Mira, Alfred; Mitchell, Bruce; Mitchell, Marie; Mohlin, Clarence; Mommer, Paul (Peter Paul); Morgan, Florence; Morosoff, Vladimir; Morse, Sam; Morton, Jay; Mose, Eric; Mosseller, Lillian M.; Mougel, Max; Mousseau, Roland; Muhlback, Ferdinand; Murphy, M. Lois; Murray, George; Murrell, Sara; Myers, Jerome
    - MacIver, Loren, 1938-1968 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Malinow, Harry, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Mark, Bendor (Marcus, Bernard), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Mattei, Antonio, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - McCormick, Linda (Matteo, L.), 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - McGee, Dorothy, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - McNeil, George, 1940-1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Mecklem, Austin, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Meltsner, Paul, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - N, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Forms for the following artists: Nadell, Rose; Nagai, Thomas; Nakagawa, Kikudo (Kokota); Nakamizo, Fuji; Nakian, Reuben; Nalband, K.; Nankivell, Frank; Nash, Ginerva; Nason, Alfred; Nastasi, Frank; Neal, Rose A.; Neigherbauer, R.; Nelson, Bruce; Nelson, Gideon; Nesin, George; Netter, Cecile; Netzer, Edward J.; Newman, Benjamin; Niberg, Abbey; Nichols, John; Nicolosi, Joseph; Nisanoff, Louis; Noble, Carl; Nooney, Ann
    - Nadelman, Elie, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Nelson, Ralph, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Newell, James Michael, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Nisanoff, Carol Weinstock, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Noguchi, Isamu, 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Norman, Geoffrey R., circa 1938 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - O, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Forms for the following artists: Oley, Moses; Ominsky, Frank; Oppenheimer, Paul; Ostrowsky, Ella; O'Temple, Marc; Owen, William
    - Olmsted, Anna W., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - P, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      Forms for the following artists: Pagliuca, Anthony; Paleologue, Jean; Palter, Rebecca; Paltorack, N.; Pantufhoff, Igor; Parker, Cushman; Pass, Morris; Patterson, Claude A.; Pecci, Mario; Peck, Augustus; Pell, Jacob; Pels, Albert; Perkins, Arlene; Perkins, Harnly (Harnley); Perner, Concetta; Peroutka, Joseph; Perper, Marc; Perry, Roland; Peszel, Jean; Peters, Carl W.; Phelps, William D.; Phillip, Robert; Phillips, G.; Phillips, L.; Piccoli, Girolamo; Pierce, Waldo; Pimentel, Palmyra; Pine, Geri; Pious, Robert; Plogsted, Louis; Poirier, Emily; Polos, Theodore C.; Polowetski, Charles; Portugal, Fred; Potter, Albert; Pratt, Herbert W.; Preachen (Preacher), William; Pulver, Joseph
    - Pandolfini, Joseph, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Pechar, Stanley, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Pereira, Irene Rice, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Pettrich, Valentino, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Poirier, Elsie J., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Pollak, Frances M., circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Poor, Anne, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Pougialis, Constantine, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Prestopino, Gregorio, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Purvey, James, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Quirt, Walter, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - R-Ri, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      Forms for the following artists: Rabinowitz, Isaac; Rabkin, Esay; Raboy, Mac; Rajer, Joseph; Rajev, J.; Rappaport, Harry; Ratzker, Max; Rebajes, Ramon Sebastian; Rehman, Harriet H.; Reid, Oliver Richard; Reina, Salvatore; Reinhardt, A.D. (Steward); Reiss, Hilda; Reno, Paul; Resnick, Benjamin; Resnick, Max; Revzan, Daniel; Reznikoff, Max; Reznikoff, Misha; Ribbecke, Robert N.; Richardson, A. De Leon; Richardson, Fred; Richman, Lillian; Richman, Virginia; Richter, Lillian; Richter, Mischa; Richter, Nathan; Rico, Dan; Rites, Marion; Riza, Janet
    - Rj-Rz, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      Forms for the following artists: Robbins, David; Robbins, Hulda D.; Robinson, J.H.D.; Rodvogin, Harris; Rogers, Julia; Rohde, Gilbert; Rohland, Caroline S.; Rohowsky, Meyer; Rollins, Lloyd L.; Rollins, Victor; Romaine, Dorothy; Ronay, Stephen; Rose, Eleanor; Rose, Herman; Rosen, Judith; Rosen, Paula; Rosenbluth, Harry; Rosenthal, Martin; Rosenwald, Janet; Ross, Fred; Ross, Louis; Roszak, Theodore J.; Rothenberg, Joseph; Roy, Suzanne; Rubenstein, Jules; Rubenstein, Morris; Rubin, Lewis; Ruelos, Eleanor; Ruggles, Philo B.; Ruhl, John; Ruiz de Rivera, Jose; Rush, Rosa; Rutledge, John; Ryan, Charles B.; Ryan, James H.
    - Raskin, Saul, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Rein, Harry, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Ribak, Louis, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Riefstahl, Elizabeth, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Robus, Hugo, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Rosenborg, Ralph, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Rothkowitz, Marcus, 1937-1967 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Rothkranz, L., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Rowe, William B., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - S-Sc, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      Forms for the following artists: Sabalauskas (Sabaslauskas), Joseph; Sackerman, Gilbert; Safferson, Matthew; Sambugnac, Alexander; Samuels, Irving K.; Samuels, Jeff; Sanborn, Gordon; Sanders, William; Sandler, Selita; Sanger, William; Santillo, Lorenzo; Sarkadi, Leo; Savage, Augusta C.; Saviano, Thomas; Sawyer, Archibald D.; Scarano, Gerard; Scaravaglione, Concetta; Schardt, Bernard; Schewe, Theodore; Schiff, Luba; Schlein, Charles; Schmid, M.; Schneider, Samuel A.; Schoonmaker, Eugene; Schrader, Gustav; Schwandt, Marion W.; Schwartz, Manfred; Scibetta, Angelo; Scoon, Carolyn; Scott, Cyril Kay; Scott, Phyllis Crawford; Scrymser, Christabel
    - Sd-So, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      Forms for the following artists: Seabrooke, Georgette; Seegert, Helen; Sehlmeyer, Caroline; Seibert, Leonard; Seltzer, Leo; Semons, Lillian; Serlin, Louis; Sever, Alfredo; Shack (Schack), William; Shahn, Tillie G.; Shampanier, Abram; Sharp, John; Shearwood, William P.; Sherlock, Genevieve M.; Shiren, Alvin; Shirley, Margot; Shoulberg, Harry; Shulgold, William; Shulman, Morris; Shutz, Viola; Silvay, Van; Silver, N.; Silverman, Gisella; Sklar, Sarah; Skolfield, Raymond; Slifkin, Abraham; Sloan, Howard A.; Small, Gerard; Smith, Inez; Smith, Judson; Snader, Arthus; Snipper, Martin; Soini, William; Soles, William; Solomon, Joe; Soroka, Albert; Sorter, David; South, John; Sovensky, Isidor
    - Sp-Sz, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      Forms for the following artists: Spagna, Vincent; Spangenbergh, G.; Spear, Devah; Spector, George; Spellens, Irving; Spreckley, Nathaniel; Springer, Ruth; Springhorn, Carl; Spurbeck, John; Squeres, C.; Stahlback (Stalback), A.; Staloff, Jack; Starr, Maxwell B.; Stearn, Frank; Stefano, Berthe; Stein, Hirch; Steinberg, Abraham; Steinberg, Isidore; Steinfeld, Lawrence; Steinlauf, Saul; Stelbach, Anna; Sterling, James; Sternberg, Harry; Sterud, Olga; Stott, Joseph; Sutton, Karl W.; Swerdloff, Sam; Swisher, Allan; Swock, Louis E.; Szilvasy, May
    - Sanger, William, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Sarlin, Louis, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Schachtman, Joseph, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Schaefer, Paul H., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Schankenberg, Henry, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Schanker, Louis, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Schlazer, Michael, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Schmitz, Carl L., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Schnitzer, Max, 1942-1967 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Seitz, William C., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Shahn, Ben, 1938-1967 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Sherman, Effim H., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Shibley, Gertrude, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Shields, Francis, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Sievan, Maurice, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Smith, Herndon E., circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Soriano, Esteban, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Soyer, Raphael, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Spiegel, Doris, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Springweiler, Erwin, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Stavenitz, Alex R., circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Stea, Cesare, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Stein, Harold, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Stella, Joseph, 1937-1967 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Stern, Louis Lionel, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Stillman, Ary, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Swantees, Ethel Lucille, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Swinden, Albert, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - T, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 71)
      Forms for the following artists: Talbot, David; Tamotzuu, Chuzo; Tanzer, Julius; Tarantino, John; Taylor, Douglas; Taylor, Frieda L.; Teller, Sara; Tercuzzi, John H.; Terrell, Elizabeth; Thal, Victor; Thaon, Joseph Francis; Theobold, Samuel; Thorp (Thorpe), George; Tobias, Abraham J.; Tobias, Mary; Tomlin, Bradley Walker; Tofel, Jennings; Tolegian, Manuel J.; Toohey, John; Topolosky, A.; Townsend, Lee; Tranum, Carl K.; Trent, Victor Pedtrotti; Tschacbasov, Nathan; Tuccio, Amelia
    - Takis, Nicholas, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Taskey, Harry Leroy, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Tishler, Harold, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Trekur, Michael, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Tromka, Alexander, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Trubach, Ernest, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Turner, Raymond, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Twining, Yvonne, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Tworkov, Jack, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Tyler, Hugh, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Ulreich, Edward B., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Usui, Bumpei, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - V, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 85)
      Forms for the following artists: Vaghjian, Edward; Vagis, Polygnotos; Valenta, Yaroslav Henry; Van de Kieft, Gerard; Van Felix, Maurice; Van Raalte, David; Vogel, Joseph; Volpe, M.A.; Volpe, Nicholas; Volz, Herman; Von-Paulin, M. Rosenschield
    - Van Aalten, Jacques, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Van Beek, William, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Velonis, Anthony, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Vidar, Frede, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Von Groschwitz, Gustave, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Von Mickwitz, Katherine, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Von Urban, Charles, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - W, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 93)
      Forms for the following artists: Wald, Sylvia; Wallace, Alfred; Wallace, Frederick; Walsh, Bernard; Walters, Carl; Walton, Kalamein; Warren, Alonzo; Warren, Wilbert; Webb, Albert; Wein, Elsie; Weinstock, Sol; Weiss, Hugo; Weiss, Julius; Weiss, N.; Wenger, Frank; Westmacott, Bernard; Whitaker, R.; White, Theodore; Wicker, Dorothy; Widlicka, Leopold; Wiegand, Hilmar; Wilks, Louis; Williams, Alexander; Wiltz, Arnold; Winograd, Illeana; Witten, Bunty; Wittmer, George; Wolfsohn (Wolfson), Arthur; Wong, Har Ling; Wood, Robert S.; Woolf, Rose
    - Walinska, Anna, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Ward, Edgar Meville, II, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Warneke, Heinz, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Warsager, Hyman, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Washburn, Kenneth, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Wein, Albert, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Weisman, David, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Weiss, Ernest A., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Weissbuch, Oscar, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Weller, Paul, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - West, John T., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Wheelock, Warren, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - White, Victor, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Williams, Mildred E., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Williamson, Scott, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Wilson, Ben, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Wilson, Reginald, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Wilson, Sol, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Winter, Charlotte, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Woiceske, Ronan W., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Wolfe, Jack, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Wolff, Adolf, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - X-Y, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 116)
      Forms for the following artists: Xceron, Jean; Ximenez, Alfredo; Yainoto, Kanamo; Yoffe, Vladimir; Youngs, Jesse M.
    - Yamasaki, Chikamachi, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Yurchenko, Basil, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Z, circa 1967 (Box 6, Folder 119)
      Forms for the following artists: Zaidenberg, A.; Zakine, Eugene; Zemachson (Zemackson), Samuel; Ziegler, Lee Woodward; Zito, Emilio
    - Zaidenberg, Arthur, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Zeeman, Bernard E., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Zilzer, Gyula, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Zion, Ben, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Zitter, Hirsch, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Zucker, Jacques, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Zunser, C. Shomer, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Zwerkoff, John, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Computer Coding Forms of Employment Histories, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Computer Data Printouts, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Computer Printouts of Employment Histories, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - WPA Artists' Essays, 1936-1965; 1.4
    Essays are by WPA artists reflecting on their experiences in the program, which were collected in 1936 by the Washington office of the WPA/FAP to be published in a national report. By 1943, plans to publish were put on hold indefinitely until the manuscript was rediscovered by O'Connor in 1968 and published under the title Art for the Millions. Several of these files also contain multiple drafts, copies, and photographs of artists intended to be published alongside their essays.
    - Anonymous, "Florida Galleries of the Federal Art Project", circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - Anonymous, "What an Art Center Can Do for Phoenix", circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Abbott, Berenice, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - Bear, Donald J., circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - Bennett, Gwendolyn, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - Benson, Emanuel M., circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - Bird, Elzy J., circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Bloch, Julius, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Bloch, Lucienne, circa 1935-1939 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Block, Lou, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Boag, Robert, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Britton, Edgar, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Brown, Douglas, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Bruton, Helen, circa 1935-1939 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - Bufano, Beniamino, circa 1935-1939 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Cashwan, Samuel, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Cervantez, Pedro, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Clapp, Thaddeus, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Clark, Adele, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Cornelius, Charles, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Cronbach, Robert, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Crosby, Hildegarde, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Curtis, Philip, circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Danysh, Joseph A., circa 1938 (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - Davis, Stuart, circa 1939 (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Defenbacher, Daniel S., circa 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Diller, Burgoyne, circa 1935-1938 (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - Dwight, Mabel, circa 1939 (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - Eichenberg, Fritz, circa 1940 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Erwin, Gene, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Evergood, Philip, circa 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Feitelson, Lorser, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Floethe, Richard, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Gellert, Hugo, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Gershoy, Eugenie, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Gettens, Rutherford J., circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Glassgold, C. Adolph, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Goodwin, Jean, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Gorky, Arshile, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Graham, Ralph, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Greene, Balcomb, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Gregory, Waylande, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Guglielmi, O. Louis, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Haupers, Clement, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Hayes, Vertis, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Heiberg, Einar, circa 1939 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Hiler, Hilaire, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Hord, Donal, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Hunter, R. Vernon, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Hynson, Garret, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Jacobi, Eli, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Jones, Lawrence A., circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Knaths, Karl, circa 1920-1936 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Knight, Frederic, circa 1932-1936 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Lamore, Chet, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Lemmon, Warren W., circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Levine, Jack, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Limbach, Russel T., circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Ludins, Eugene, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - MacDonald-Wright, Stanton, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Marantz, Irving J., circa 1936-1938 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - McMahon, Audrey, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Millman, Edward, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Morris, Carl, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Morsell, Mary, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Moylan, Lloyd, circa 1939 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Murray, Hester Miller, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Newell, James Michael, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Norman, Geoffrey, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Ogburn, Hilda Lanier, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Olds, Elizabeth, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Palo-Kangas, Uno John, circa 1938 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Piccoli, Girolamo, circa 1939 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Pierce, Harold K., circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Pollak, Frances, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Quirt, Walter, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Rackley, Mildred, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Richardson, Antonio, circa 1939 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Rothschild, Lincoln, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Rourke, Constance, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Sears, Arthur W., circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Sheets, Nan, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Siporin, Mitchell, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Smith, Cecil, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Smith, David, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Smith, E. Herndon, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Smith, Gordon M., circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Sommer, William, circa 1939 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Speck, Walter E., circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Spivak, Max, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Stavenitz, Alexander R., circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Sutton, Harry H., circa 1939 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Swelander, Vivian, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Thorp, George C., circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Trentham, Eugene, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Velonis, Anthony, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Viviano, Emmanuel, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Von Groschwitz, Gustave, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Warsager, Hyman, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Weisenborn, Rudolph, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - White, Francis Robert, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Wolff, Robert Jay, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Wulf, Lloyd, circa 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1935-1965 (Box 7, Folder 76)
- Publications, 1939-1985; Series 2; 4.3 Linear feet Boxes 7-11, BV 25-26, OV 27
  This series contains research files and administrative materials related to O'Connor's publications on the WPA/FAP and New Deal artists, Federal Support for the Visual Arts: The New Deal and Now (1969), New Deal Art Projects: An Anthology of Memoirs (1972), Art for the Millions (1973), and Federal Art Patronage Notes (publication, 1974-1984). Documents include correspondence with publishers, research notes, financial records, drafts, proofs, and final reports.
  The series is arranged as 4 subseries. Materials are arranged by document type.
  2.1: Federal Support for the Visual Arts: The New Deal and Now, 1939-1985
  2.2: New Deal Art Projects: An Anthology of Memoirs, 1968-1972
  2.3: Art for the Millions, 1965-1973
  2.4: Federal Art Patronage Notes, 1971-1985
  - Federal Support for the Visual Arts: The New Deal and Now, 1939-1985; 2.1
    Correspondence, drafts, administrative records, research data, computer printouts, and final reports related to O'Connor's National Endowment sponsored project, Federal Support for the Visual Arts (FSVA). This project was an analysis to measure the effectiveness of New Deal art projects by tracing the history of the projects, surveying the subsequent careers of participating artists, and measuring the economic value of surviving artworks where possible. The project's final report was published in 1969 and references documentation collected in Series 1.1-1.3.
    - Administrative, Account Registers, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Administrative, D.C. Zoning, circa 1968 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Administrative, Project Bills, circa 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Administrative, Staff, circa 1968-1985 (Box 7, Folder 80-81)
    - Administrative, Tax Reporting (D.C.), circa 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Administrative, Tax Reporting (federal), circa 1968 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Correspondence, Committee to Save New Deal Art, circa 1970 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Correspondence, Early Press on New Deal, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Correspondence, Early Research and Proposals, 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Correspondence, General Research Inquiries, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 87-88)
    - Correspondence, Final Report and Press Coverage, circa 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Correspondence, Form Letters to Artists and Press, circa 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Correspondence, NCFA Deposit of Research Files, circa 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, NCFA General Information, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Draft, Artist and Index/Subject Lists, circa 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)